LAYLA ALMARWANI

Vancouver, BC

7783864374

Laylaalmarwani.top@gmail.com



Skills

React HTML & CSS Javascript

Ruby on Rails Node.js Express. DATABASE PostgreSQL

DEVELOPMENT &
OPERATIONS
Git Github NPM
Webpack Hiroku

Knowledge

Python & C++

EDUCATION

WEB

DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

CodeCore College 2020 - 2021

Computer science Diploma TVTC, Saudi Arabia August 2014-May 2017 Training on Digital Marketing, TVTC, Saudi Arabia 2016

Languages

Arabic (native)
English (fluent)

Summary:

Jr Web Developer with experience working on several projects, passionate about solving problems and learning new technologies . Background working with non-profit organizations. I enjoy building games using Python and C++ in my free time.

Projects:

THE SOCIAL HOME - THIS APPLICATION IS MADE TO BE USED BY SOCIAL WORKERS AND HOMEOWNERS.

Front End - ReactJS | Back End -Node.JS | Database - CMS

- A fast filtering and search experiences.
- Contact form to receive submissions using EmilJs.
- Updating and managing data quickly with CMS.

AUCTION - THIS WEB APPLICATION IS AN AUCTION SYSTEM DESIGN FOR SAILING AND BIDDING.

Front-End: React.Js | Back-End: Ruby on Rails | Database: PostgreSQL

- Users are able to create auction and bid on items using basics CRUD.
- Tested code to provide high-quality performance using ruby libraries
- · Secure authentication.

SUPER TEAM PICKER- THIS APPLICATION IS A THE SPIN-NING WHEEL T GAME O PICK RANDOM NAMES.

Front-End: html & C | Back-End: jQuery

- Users are able to add and take names, spin the wheel multiple times.
- Secure authentication.
- Interactive music and animation.

Work Experience:

Accor Bullman Zamzam Hotel, Medina SA

Guest Relations - Data Management - August 2017 - November 2017 Quality management database admin. Administer and maintain quality management database in HotSOS

- Record quality incidents based on customer feedback
- Develop periodic quality analytics on guest experience
- Maintain record of monthly quality trends and drive quality improvement initiatives in lagging departments

ISSofBC, Burnaby BC

Volunteer Interpreter/Administrative Assistant - March 2018 - April 2018

- Simultaneous in person translation of Arabic to English and vice versa to assist refugees and asylum seekers in settlement in Canada
- Ensure that the clients and volunteers understood each other.
- Entered client tax data into IRCC database.
- Answered phone calls. Organized meetings for supervisor and team members.

Frog Hollow Neighbourhood House, Vancouver CA

Youth worker- September 2018 - March 2020

- - Provide social, recreational, and skill development activities for youth.
- - Provide a physically and emotionally safe environment for all program participants, staff, and
- · volunteers.
- Simultaneous in person translation of Arabic to English and vice versa
- - Create and implement a plan to provide support to vulnerable youth.
- - Leading youth and advocate for them.
- - provide 1-1 settlement support to youth as required.
- Ensure programming fits within approved budgets.

•